<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-15" standalone="no"?><uc-export clientvers="11.0.0">
<DOCU name="PCK.AUTOMIC_HASHICORP_VAULT.PUB.DOC">
<HEADER state="1">
<Title>Pack Documentation</Title>
<ArchiveKey1/>
<ArchiveKey2/>
<OH_SubType/>
</HEADER>
<DOCU_Docu state="1" type="text">
<DOC><![CDATA[About the Package
HashiCorp Vault secures, stores, and tightly controls access to tokens, passwords, certificates, API keys, and other secrets in modern computing. Action pack is used to fetch Secrets
of credentials stored on Hashicorp vault for AWS and KV Engine.

=Setup=
* This Action pack supports Windows and UNIX Agent.
* Vault command line interface should be available on agent OS and set as executable in PATH environment variable.
* Oracle JRE 1.7 or higher version should be installed on agent OS.
* Java executable should be set in the PATH environment variable on agent OS.  
* To run the action on Windows, Power shell 4.0 or higher version should be installed.
 

=Common Inputs=
Vault Base URL*: Provide Vault Base URL to connect. E.g. https://10.243.44.110:8200/
Username:        Provide Username to authenticate. E.g. User1
Password:        Provide Password to authenticate.
Token:           Provide token to authenticate on Vault.
HTTP Options:    Specify one ore more following options for this parameter if you want to use certificates. 
                 Multiple options can be provided using space separator. E.g. -ca-cert=/opt/vault/ca-cert.pem -client-cert=/opt/vault/client.pem
                 -ca-cert=<string>  Path on the Agent OS to a single PEM-encoded CA certificate to verify the Vault server's SSL certificate.
                 -ca-path=<string>  Path on the Agent OS to a directory of PEM-encoded CA certificates to verify the Vault server's SSL
                                    certificate.
                 -client-cert=<string> Path on the Agent OS to a single PEM-encoded CA certificate to use for TLS authentication to the 
                                       Vault server. If this is specified -client-key is also required.
                 -client-key=<string>  Path on the Agent OS to a single PEM-encoded private key matching the client certificate 
                                       from -client-cert.
                -tls-server-name=<string> Name to use as the SNI host when connecting to the Vault server via TLS.
                -tls-skip-verify Disable verification of TLS certificates.
                 


=Note=
- Please provide either Token or Username and Password to connect the vault.

=Actions=
Following actions are supported.

* Action name: PCK.AUTOMIC_HASHICORP_VAULT.PUB.ACTION.GET_AWS_SECRET
* Action Description: This action is used to retrieve Access Key and Secret Key from Hashicorp Vault using AWS secret engine.

* Action name: PCK.AUTOMIC_HASHICORP_VAULT.PUB.ACTION.GET_KV_SECRET
* Action Description: This action fetches the Value corresponding to Key of a secret from Hashicorp Vault using KV secret engine.

]]></DOC>
</DOCU_Docu>
</DOCU>
</uc-export>